Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Attention. customers.
The pool is now closed.
Please make
your way to the exit.
What are you doing here?
OK.
Wait. Fuck. Don't.
Stop.
Fuckin' hell.
Calm the fuck down.
Oh.
Reckon I could get up there?
What?
Snakes and heights.
Right.
Fuck me.
What makes you think
you can pick that up?
I can do it.
Oh. fuck.
Funnel-web.
On your shoulder.
Just don't move. alright?
Fuck you. you cunt.
What?
What the fuck was that?
Do it one more time.
Fuck.
Fuck you doing?!
There anything
you're not afraid of?
Huh?
We should go.
Yeah. OK.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know. is it a good
thing or a bad thing? Is it...
It's not even a thing.
Yeah. but. like. come on.
Come on. what?
You ignore me at school
and then you just ask me
to hang out?
Like. it doesn't make
any sense.
I don't ignore you.
Yes. you do.
We're at school.
you're so different.
And then you're with just me.
Give me a fucking
example of how I'm different.
- Hmm.
- Hmm. Hmm.
-By the way you act. talk...
-Can't think of one.
..speak. walk.
Everything about you.
I'm the exact same cunt
I've always been. mate.
You're not.
Get down. Get down.
Get off me.
OK.
Been there before?
The...the mill?
Nah. First time.
You?
Yeah. first time.
Cool.
Don't tell anyone about it.
The mill.
Yeah. nah. I...I won't.
See you later?
Yeah.
Will she accept love
into her life?
And by accepting God's love.
she will be prepared
to make free choices.
The free choices
that will bring her here.
To confess her sins.
Because we recognise
both the physical
and the spiritual
responsibility of parenthood.
Now I'm sure
you're all sick of
the sound of my voice.
I know I am.
So I'd love it if we could
all come together now
and pray for this little one.
♪ Blackest shadows
♪ In the poison
Taste it
♪ Call my name
♪ And I would come to face it
♪ Everything that you created
♪ Yeah
♪ Everything that is broken
washes away
♪ I turn to you. my devotion
Show me the way
♪ Everything that is sacred
softens the pain
♪ I know it's you
I'm not shaken
♪ Show me the way
♪ Everything that is broken
washes away
♪ I turn to you. my devotion
Show me the way
♪ Everything that is sacred
softens... ♪
How old do you reckon
that mum was?
Naim!
Probably 12.
But. you know. there are
older kids here too.
Mum.
Sally Frankston's into
that psych trance stuff
you listen to.
It's actually. um. psytrance
and I haven't listened to it
since we moved here.
You haven't made
any friends either.
Mum. don't.
Psytrance?
How long have I
been calling it psych?
About three years.
I bet you thought
that was funny.
Still do.
Arlene.
You. uh. you must be Naim.
I'm Rod.
Uh. you...you know my son.
Hunter. from school.
Hey. bro.
Arlene. have you. um. have you
thought about it some more?
Your story?
I mean. it really. really
doesn't have to be much.
And it was. um. it was late
and the sky had this.
like. orange stripe in it.
And. um...
There was these bells.
like. these fake tinny bells.
and she was just like.
"God's ringing for you. Naim.
"Listen."
And I just said.
"Mum. I'm sick of
your fucking bullshit.
"It's just a fucking
ice-cream truck."
And then she just said.
"One day. one day. Naim.
"you'll...you'll believe in
things that you can't see."
And then she laughed
some more.
She used to laugh a lot.
I shouldn't have told you
that. I'm...I'm sorry.
You shouldn't be.
Do you like it here?
What?
What do you like
about this place?
Nah. my...my mum
wanted to move here.
Said she...belonged.
To what?
People who believed.
I don't know.
Some...some bullshit.
Now...stuck in this shithole.
So...nothing then?
What?
There's nothing you like
about this place?
Nah.
Nothing.
I knew what he was
doing. He was just walking.
Because if he was
out there walking.
we wouldn't
have to talk about it.
I knew this awful thing
was coming for Tom.
For both of us. really.
And I'd just sit at home
in this terrifying silence.
But I found someone else
in that silence.
Someone who'd listen.
Who'd talk about death.
but...above all. about life.
Jesus is in that silence.
And I love that silence now.
It makes me feel...safe.
"Die not. poor Death
"Nor yet canst thou kill me
"From rest and sleep
"Which but thy pictures be
"Much pleasure; then from thee
much more must flow.
"And soonest our best..."
Really?
No.
Naim. you sure
we can't get you anything?
Tea. water. juice?
How about a beer?
- He thinks he's funny.
- I am funny.
We don't drink.
Izzie?
Thank you.
So...
You. um...
You wanna tell us
what's going on?
Is your mum OK?
I know you've both been
through a lot.
You won't tell Hunter
I came by?
Please. don't tell
either of them.
You. uh.
been to one of these before?
Yeah.
It's just another one
of these shows
my parents put on
for these gullible arseholes.
Yeah. right.
My dad's one of them
fucking gullible arseholes.
Reckon that guy
can make it stop?
Make what stop?
- You feel it?
- No. thanks.
Tell us
what you're feeling.
Um...
It's kind of cold in here.
I guess.
That's good.
Cold is good.
There's glory
in all temperatures.
All the suffering...
There you go.
That's your healing.
Do you feel it?
Uh. not...not really. no.
I just feel colder
than before.
That's the power
of God closing in on you.
All your lust.
all your indecency.
all your desire.
it has to go now.
Not tomorrow but now.
Right now.
Now look.
Look at the light.
By the power
of your holy flame.
make new what was defiled.
Two fires. O Lord.
One to defile
and one to reform.
The sons of Aaron
brought fire
to please themselves.
They worshipped
as they willed.
Rod. what's going on?
So the fire
of judgement fell.
- Ryan!
- Hunter?
What's happening?
Hunter?
Hunter? Hunter?
What's happening?
Rod. what's happening?
What's going on?
Please. Someone.
help him breathe! Please!
The sons of Aaron
brought fire
to please themselves.
They worshipped
as they willed.
And so the fire
of judgement fell.
- Hunter!
- Hold his head.
Hunter! It's me.
Look at me.
Ryan. please!
By the fire that consumes.
I call upon the judgement.
Let the fire fall now!
End it now!
Somebody!
Somebody do something!
I'm scared here.
♪ Doors are open
♪ And I believe
♪ I believe that
every mountain
♪ Has your name
carved in the bottom
♪ I believe
that every river... ♪
Oh. Oh. my God.
Yeah.
What. cunt?
Fucking loser.
Oh! Oh!
Stay on the road. mate.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Ryan?
Your mum's gonna see us.
They'll find out
about you too.
You OK?
Come on.
You have to stop.
Stop what?
- I can't.
- Naim?
Oh. mate.
Let's go on the road. mate.
Told you not here.
They'll see us.
You sure there's no-one here?
Are you sure?
Come on then.
Come on.
Be quiet. yeah?
Lucky they're fucking always
hid away in their bedroom.
Yeah. but what
if there's people here?
Yeah. OK. Let's just try it.
Thought you were scared.
Are you gonna do it too?
Just me.
Oh. my God.
That's pathetic.
Ryan. Ryan!
Fuck.
-Stop following me!
-Ryan. Ryan.
Stop doing this.
Stop coming to my house.
What was that?
You!
It was you!
Please. don't make me
tell anyone.
Just leave me alone.
Please.
Hey!
Chips!
That guy at your house
the other night.
what did he do to you?
It's worked
on kids all over.
In Redbay. there was a girl.
There was a guy in Mount
Harvey had it done to him.
He's got kids now.
That's what I heard.
So did it work?
On you?
Why are you asking?
What about Ryan?
Did it work on him?
It's every night.
When I close up...
..he comes here.
He shouldn't be
doing it anymore.
Doing what?
He just throws shit at me.
-No. right.
-When he comes here.
-No. I just meant...
-We don't do anything else.
Why doesn't anyone
fucking believe me?
Hunter!
Hunter! Hunter!
Hunter. no!
Hunter. stop!
No. stop!
Hunter!
Hunter. no. Stop!
Hunter! Hunter!
Oh. Hunter. no!
Hunter. Wait!
Hunter?! Hunter?!
Hunter. where are you?
Hunter!
It did something to him.
-Then that thing killed him!
-Alright. OK.
Naim. I am not your enemy. OK?
I'm here to help you but I can
only do that if you stay calm.
Alright?
Is everything OK at home?
You know. with you
and with your mum?
What?
Well. it's just sometimes
when we're dealing with
something
and it's too hard to accept.
we deny it.
You know. we push it away.
We try to replace that truth
with something else.
-Another story.
-I felt it at the servo.
And I felt it
at the photo booth!
Naim. OK?
We all want the same thing.
The police are working on it.
But...
..if you really wanna help us.
you have to be honest.
What you're describing.
this thing you're describing.
it sounds impossible.
It's coming for Ryan.
It's gonna kill him!
OK. they will come in here
and they will charge you
with disrupting
an investigation.
Can you just... Please!
Is that what
you want me to do?
Do anything. please! I just...
It's gonna kill him!
Just...
I've had this feeling...
..all my life that I'm...
..that I've been scared of.
And ever since we moved.
I really got
more scared of it.
Because Ryan and I...
..we shared the same feeling.
We got together.
Like. we got together.
And it was exciting.
But it totally made me
feel more scared.
Now. I don't want you
to worry. OK?
-We'll speak to someone.
-Uh. Hunter's dad.
Um. I don't know.
He runs the church.
He might know
where to find that guy.
-The deliverance healer.
-We'll look into it.
I promise. OK?
Thank you.
Sergeant.
I'll be out in a minute.
Who's that?
Mum?
I've been
thinking. Naim.
Maybe there's always
gonna be kids
who...hurt people like Hunter.
People like Ryan.
Like you.
That woman with the police
says she sees it all the time.
She reckons it's that kind of
hate that killed Hunter.
I just...
I can't lose you too.
I'm sorry.
Mum. no.
No. you can't do this.
Please. I can't.
No. you can't do this. Mum!
Mum! Mum!
Get off me!
Settle down.
No. you can't do this!
Get off me!
Mum. they killed Hunter! Mum!
Mate. mate.
You don't wanna do this!
- It's OK.
- Please. don't! Let go of me!
Please!
No! Get off me!
Naim. don't.
Hold still.
Argh! Stop touching me!
Look.
Two fires. O Lord.
One to defile
and one to reform.
Sons of Aaron brought fire
to please themselves.
They worshipped
as they willed.
So
the fire of judgement fell...
Hey.
They have those sausage rolls.
The ones you like.
They have pizza too.
But it has olives on it.
I took the olives off.
Ryan?
Ryan. I've been trying
to find you.
Told you to fuck off.
Ryan. just wait.
My mum took me to that guy.
-The deliverance healer.
-Why would she do that?
I don't know.
Ever since we moved here.
she can't face
anything that's real.
I don't know what to do.
Fuck!
- Help! Help!
- You right. mate?
-He tried to...
-Who?
Him!
Ohh.
Fuck!
Hey! Naim.
Stay the fuck away from me!
You saw it. didn't you?
- What did it look like?
- Naim! Ryan.
They did it to you too.
didn't they?
Come with me.
Come on.
These kids
at a camp I went to.
they said a couple of girls
went to that guy.
the deliverance healer.
And after.
one of them died at the pool.
Some people said she slipped.
I don't know. I thought
it was just a dumb story.
So why are you telling us?
My brother...
My brother saw it.
I didn't believe it.
What about the other one?
You said the guy did it
to two of them.
Jessica.
And now she just hangs out
at the Murryville Hospital
all day and night.
Why?
It comes for you
when you're alone.
The hospital's
the only place that's...
Izzie.
your mum wants you.
Murryville. that's about
an hour away.
Right?
Do you think she's right?
About being alone with it?
I'm sorry.
Jessica?
You lost?
You knew a girl. Marnie?
You kids shouldn't be in here.
We just wanna know
about that guy.
The deliverance healer.
Yeah. well. I don't know
where he is.
If you find him. trust me. you
don't want what he's selling.
It's too late.
What the fuck
is this thing?
Well. what did you see?
It always looks like
the person you're the most...
You know.
Into.
And it doesn't matter
who it is.
Best friend. Movie star.
Gym teacher you once
had a crush on.
It knows.
So. um...
So you think Marnie saw you?
When she died?
Yeah. you can go now.
I can't help you.
No. I didn't mean...
Just stay around other people.
No. I shouldn't
have said that.
I said fuck off!
Sorry. We just thought you'd
know how to make it stop.
You can't make it stop.
Nothing can make it stop.
- We should have split up.
- Hey!
It gets better
at looking like you
and touching like you.
We've talked about this. Your
friends need to leave now.
I...I...I am serious.
Can we get some
security backup down here?
Stay away from your friend.
You are only making it worse.
You are only making it worse!
Stay away!
Come on. You're
not even a patient in here.
Let's go. Naim. Come on.
Hey. you missed someone.
Can we let him on quickly?
Hey. you alright?
Naim.
Fuck.
Hey. hey. hey.
Hey. look at me. Naim.
Hey. it can't get you.
There's people right here.
Naim. It can't get you.
Hey. I'm here. Fuck. open it!
Hey.
Hey. It's alright. Naim.
it's alright. It's alright.
Look at me. Hey. it's alright.
I'll go away.
What?
What if she's right?
What if we're only
making it stronger?
Don't go.
I hate that shithole anyway.
I know you do. Naim.
-You don't?
-Yeah. I do.
Don't go.
It's all my fault.
Please.
It's OK.
Oh. my God.
You're hopeless.
Yeah.
she should get away with you.
Thanks. yeah.
'Cause. like. I know. like.
they'll be. like.
getting the bus.
-I don't want her with us.
-Yeah.
I'm gonna miss it again!
I'm so sorry.
Ohh!
- Ryan?
- Ryan!
- Oh. Oh. my God!
- In here!
OK. Ryan. um.
just...just. like...
Wait. Ryan. just wait.
What happened?
Who...who did that?
-Oh. my God.
-Oh! Oh!
I know you miss him.
Come on. please. honey.
Come home.
Come home. please.
Come home with me. Come home.
Please come home.
Please. honey.
Bus we took
to Murryville.
Goes to the city.
Don't follow me.
What?
You shouldn't be near me.
I shouldn't be
near you either.
Right.
OK. so you leave town.
Then what?
It's just gonna look like
the next dickhead you're into.
And the next one after that.
If I'm gonna live with
this thing. then...
..I don't want it to look like
some other dickhead.
I want it to look like you.
You sure your parents
aren't gonna freak?
About the car.
Nuh. My dad's the one
who told me where to find him.
That guy that did this to you.
He'll know
how to take it back.
Where is he?
What is this. Izzie?
He's gonna do it here?
Izzie?
My dad left yesterday.
He just packed up his stuff
and left.
Izzie. what the fuck
is going on?
He told me I didn't do
anything wrong.
He said I should stop
blaming myself
for what happened to Hunter.
It only happened because of
how you made him feel.
And because you told
my parents about it.
Do you wanna tell him
or should I?
Ryan...
Naim. what the fuck's
she talking about?
What are we doing out here?
Shouldn't be out this late.
you know?
Two boys...
..like you.
Ryan!
-Ryan!
-Come on!
-Let's get the sticks!
-Bitch!
Ryan!
Hit him in the head!
Come on!
Hold him down.
Grab him!
Ryan. stop!
That's my parents' car!
- Watch out!
- Ryan!
Ryan. wait!
Ryan!
Ryan.
-I'm sorry.
-Go inside.
I only told them about
you and Hunter because...
Get out of the car.
Now.
OK.
Naim.
If you see anything
that looks like me...
..don't go near it.
It won't be me.
-Ryan...
-It'll never be me.
What the fuck?!
Mum?
What's going on?
You can't leave me alone
like that.
What are you talking about?
There's this thing. It comes
when no-one else is around.
What thing?
It looks like Ryan.
There's a kid that
looks like Ryan?
-He do something to you?
-No. It's not like that.
It just looks like Ryan
'cause it always looks like...
Like what? Can you show me?
No-one else can see it.
Only us.
Mum.
Mum. did you hear what I said?
I think sometimes at your age
other kids can make you feel
a whole lot of things
you don't really feel.
I think Ryan
got in your head...
No. it's not that.
..and made you
believe in something
that's not really you.
-What did he do to me?!
-Naim.
-OK. to us?
-Naim!
Surely you know
something about it!
Naim. stop.
Please don't lie to me.
And please...
..move your stuff
from my room.
You'll need to make
your own dinner.
This is Arlene.
Leave a message. thanks.
Naim.
Naim. Open the door.
Open the fucking door.
That thing's in the backyard.
Shut up. Shut up. No. no.
I'm alone.
I know it's not you.
I don't know
if it's you either. do I?
I don't wanna be here.
I hate what
you fucking did to me.
My mum will be back soon.
She'll be pissed
if she sees you.
Yeah. but the point is
she'll see me. won't she?
Can't I just stay here then?
Until she gets back?
You know.
this is what they wanted.
Us to be scared of each other.
I am.
No. I've seen you scared.
Snake with a frog
in its mouth.
Thought you were gonna.
like. gag or something.
Fuck you.
'cause you were scared too.
Ryan.
I'm sorry I told them.
About you and Hunter.
I think I was scared.
How I felt.
About you.
I was never scared
of this. Naim.
It's so dumb.
Yeah.
Ahh!
Ahh! Ahhhh!
No. no. no. no. no.
We're gonna close
in. like. 10 minutes.
Do you see that guy?
No.
And we're closing in...
..nine minutes.
Hey. can I please just stay?
Just for a little bit?
Um...
No. you can close up.
I just...
I need to be around people.
Can I. please?
Please.
Just one. Yeah.
Just one person. please.
Anyone.
Just...just one person.
Please.
Ryan?
It's...it's me.
Naim!
It's me.
It's OK.
Please.
this is what it wanted.
It's OK.
They wanted us to be scared.
Fuck.
This is Ryan.
Leave a message.
Don't
climb up on anything in there.
If you see the boy.
if you need assistance.
wait for the paramedics.
Hey.
It'll be OK.
I reckon he just ran away.
I've been here before.
With Ryan.
I know you don't believe me...
..but ever since
you took me to that guy...
..I've been getting hurt.
Ryan's been getting hurt too.
Mum. Mum.
I can't help you.
What?
This thing can't be undone.
That's what they told me.
You knew?
They told me
it would keep you safe.
But I'm not safe.
I'm terrified!
I know.
Look. I won't be
around forever.
And we need fear. Naim.
It's how we survive.
He's not in the middle.
Let's move to
the second field. Over.
What did they tell you?
Mum!
Gather up this way.
We're moving on.
Come on.
It's getting cold.
Let the volunteers know
the boy's not here.
We're gonna move on. Over.
Just a couple of
tinnies today. thanks.
Naim?
Naim!
Oh. my back does not
go well on those seats at all.
Oh. that's alright.
My back hurts.
Please tell me
it's really you.
♪ 'Cause you see me like a UFO
♪ That's like never...
What?
Hey.
♪ 'Cause I made you use
your self-control
♪ And you made me lose
♪ My self-control.
my self-control... ♪
♪ Keep a place for me
♪ I'll sleep between y'all.
it's nothing
♪ Keep a place for me
♪ It's nothing. it's nothing
♪ I. I. I know you gotta
leave. leave. leave
♪ Take down some summertime
♪ Give up. just tonight.
night. night
♪ I. I. I know you got
someone comin'
♪ You're spittin' game.
know you got it
♪ I. I. I know you gotta
leave. leave. leave
♪ Take down some summertime
♪ Give up. just tonight.
night. night
♪ I. I. I know you got
someone comin'
♪ You're spittin' game.
know you got it
♪ Yeah
♪ I. I. I know you gotta
leave. leave. leave
♪ Take down some summertime
♪ Give up. just tonight.
night. night
♪ I. I. I know you got
someone comin'
♪ You're spittin' game.
know you got it... ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm